[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":128388,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":712665,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Do you see how +<sub>6</sub> works? By subtracting 6 every time we get above 5, we ensure t hat when  we combine two numbers using +<sub>6</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 5.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":12107,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":724793,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"9","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["9"],"rt":26674,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":751477,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":10972,"trial_type":"feed back","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":762466,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":13366,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":775841,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":2168,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":778025,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number,  and then  add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":32951,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":810985,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":2376,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":813377,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":10284,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":823680,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 2 because 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":1806,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":825492,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":5398,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":830893,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"C orrect! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":4303,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":835202,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":4405,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":839609,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":1794,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":841407,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is  1 +<sub> 6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4"],"rt":4950,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":846365,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":3317,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":849686,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you su btract 6  to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":4171,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":853861,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":2010,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":855874,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":5212,"trial_type":"questi on","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":861091,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1862,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":862955,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":4545,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":867504,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":2193,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":869703,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":19037,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":888750,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the element that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>). Sim ilarly,  3 is its own inverse under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":24253,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":913022,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":8920,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":921961,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":10995,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":932961,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 u nder +<s ub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":6728,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":939697,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1663,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":941366,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":5717,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":947085,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1685,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":948775,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4"],"rt":4142,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":952920,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, an d 0 is t he identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1933,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":954855,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["6"],"rt":4554,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":959414,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":6176,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":965594,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, an d the op eration can simply be performed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":7485,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":973084,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because 1 can make every other element under +<sub>6</sub>, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br /><br /> However, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<su b>6</sub > 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":40043,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":1013131,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Yes"],"rt":8303,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":1021454,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":5038,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":1026499,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 5  a genera tor under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":3935,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":1030441,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":4444,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":1034888,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":10716,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":1045611,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":1703,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":1047319,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":" Yes","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Yes"],"rt":4008,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":1051332,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":5634,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":1056969,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />Do you see how +<sub>9</sub> works just like +<sub>6</sub>? By subtracting 9 every time we get above 8, we ensure that when we combine two numbers using +<sub>9</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 8.<b r /><br  />We'll give you one practice question with feedback to make sure you understand the new operation. After that, try to complete the remaining questions as accurately as possible.","rt":20504,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":1077479,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":5513,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":1083012,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":1789,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":1084807,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["6"],"rt":5882,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":1090691,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":9281,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":1099977,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":4982,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":1104964,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0 ","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":4291,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":1109257,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":8874,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":1118135,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"On the following question, and several others later in the HIT, we will ask you to explain how you got your answer. On these questions, you will be given one box for your answer to the question, and a second for your explanation. Please explain your thought process in as much detail as possible (at least one sentence, and more if you can).","rt":10896,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":1129036,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":true,"explanation":"1)4+1=5  \n2)5 less than 9\n3) answer 5","explanation_history":["4+1=5  5 less than 9","14+1=5  5 less than 9","1)4+1=5  5 less than 9","1)4+1=5  \n5 less than 9","1)4+1=5  \n25 less than 9","1)4+1=5  \n2)5 less than 9\n3) answer 5"],"response_history":["5"],"rt":57866,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":1186910,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":true,"explanation":"1) 8+4=12\n2) 12 > 9\n12-9 =3","explanation_history":["1) 8+4=12\n2) 12 > 9\n12-9 =3"],"response_history":["3"],"rt":50113,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":1237041,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":true,"explanation":"you have to find a number that if added to nine you will get 9.  So 0+9=9","explanation_history":["you have to find a number that =","you have to find a number that if added to nine you will get 9.  so","you have to find a number that if added to nine you will get 9.  s","you have to find a number that if added to nine you will get 9.  So0+9=9","you have to find a number that if added to nine you will get 9.  So 0+9=9"],"response_history":["0"],"rt":85937,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":1322982,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4"],"rt":13211,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":1336197,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"7","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["7"],"rt":16631,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":1352831,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"9","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["9"],"rt":5120,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":1357953,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of  3 under  +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","explain":true,"explanation":"You need to find out what to add to 3 to get to 9.  9-3=6","explanation_history":["You need to find out what to add to 3 to get to 9.  9-3=6"],"response_history":["6"],"rt":43460,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":1401416,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","explain":true,"explanation":"you can't add odd numbers or the number 8 to get to 9","explanation_history":["you can't mu","you can't m","you can't add 8 toget to nine","you can't add 8 toget to nin","you can't add 8 toget to ni","you can't add 8 toget to n","you can't add 8 toget to ","you can't add 8 toget to","you can 't add 8 toget t","you can't add 8 toget ","you can't add 8 toget","you can't add 8 toge","you can't add 8 tog","you can't add 8 to","you can't add 8 t","you can't add 8 ","you can't add 8","you can't add odd numbers or the number 8 to get 9","you can't add odd numbers or the number 8 to get to 9"],"response_history":["No"],"rt":73067,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":1474486,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","explain":true,"explanation":"yes, you can add other numbers to it to get to nine","explanation_history":["yes, you can add other numbers to it to get to nine"],"response_history":["Yes"],"rt":24607,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":1499097,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 5  a gener ator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","explain":true,"explanation":"no  5 is not divisible to 9","explanation_history":["no  5 is not divisable to 9","no  5 is not divisible to 9"],"response_history":["No"],"rt":31528,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":1530629,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":true,"explanation":"it is not divisible to 9 ","explanation_history":["it is not divisable to 9 ","it is not divisible to 9 "],"response_history":["No"],"rt":32842,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":1563474,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd l ike to a sk you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use +_n, and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":23565,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":1587043,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"1++n=","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1++n="],"rt":23651,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":1610698,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"x-+n=","explain":true,"explanation":"you minus x by +n","explanation_history":["you mini","you minus x by +n"],"response_history":["x-+n="],"rt":39820,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":1650535,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"not sure","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["not sure"],"rt":42832,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":1693386,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":" False","response":"False","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["True","False"],"rt":12009,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":1705412,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["True"],"rt":7479,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":1712895,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a divisor of n, that is, x must divide n evenly, with no remainder.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["True"],"rt":14521,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":1727420,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"True","response":"True","explain":true,"explanation":"you have to divide x by n+.  If no numbers left over then its a divisor ","explanation_history":["you have to mulipy ","you have to mulipy","you have to mulip","you have to muli","you have to multipy ","you have to multiply  ","you have to multiply x ","you have to multiply  ","you have to multiply ","you have to multipl ","you have to multip ","you have to multi ","you have to mult ","you have to mul ","you have to mu ","you have to m ","you have to  ","you have to d ","you have to di ","you have to div ","you have to divi ","you have to divid ","you hav e to divide  ","you have to divide x  ","you have to divide x b ","you have to divide x by  ","you have to divide x by n ","you have to divide x by n+ ","you have to divide x by n+.   ","you have to divide x by n+.  I ","you have to divide x by n+.  If  ","you have to divide x by n+.  If n ","you have to divide x by n+.  If no  ","you have to divide x by n+.  If no n ","you have to divide x by n+.  If no nu ","you have to divide x by n+.  If no num ","you have to divide x by n+.  If no numb ","you have to divide x by n+.  If no number ","you have to divide x by n+.  If no numbers  ","you have to divide x by n+.  If no numbers l ","you have to divide x by n+.  If no numbers le ","you have to divide x by n+.  If no numbers lef ","you have to divide x by n+.  If no numbers left  ","you have to divide x by n+.  If no numbers left o ","you have to divide x by n+.  If no numbers left ov ","you have to divide x by n+.  If no numbers left over  ","you have to divide x by n+.  If no  numbers  left over th ","you have to divide x by n+.  If no numbers left over the ","you have to divide x by n+.  If no numbers left over then  ","you have to divide x by n+.  If no numbers left over then it ","you have to divide x by n+.  If no numbers left over then its  ","you have to divide x by n+.  If no numbers left over then its i ","you have to divide x by n+.  If no numbers left over then its  ","you have to divide x by n+.  If no numbers left over then its a  ","you have to divide x by n+.  If no numbers left over then its a d ","you have to divide x by n+.  If no numbers left over then its a di ","you have to divide x by n+.  If no numbers left over then its a div ","you have to divide x by n+.  If no numbers left over then its a divi ","you have to divide x by n+.  If no numbers left over then its a divis ","you have to divide x by n+.  If no numbers left over then its a diviso ","you have to divide x by n+.  If no numbers left over then its a divisor "],"response_history":["Tru e"],"rt":109205,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":1836633,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Always","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Always"],"rt":14467,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":1851117,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Sometimes","response":"Always","explain":true,"explanation":"x is a generator.  s o it fit s into +n.  as a result x+ will fit int oit","explanation_history":["x is a generator.  so it fits into +n.  as a result x+ will fit int oit"],"response_history":["Always"],"rt":60467,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":1911587,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Sometimes","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":31883,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":1943476,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background. Please press Continue to continue.","rt":3970,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":1947461,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"50","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["50"],"rt":4167,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":1951637,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"Some college, no degree","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Some college, no degree"],"rt":4723,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":1956363,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is the mo st advan ced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Alegrbra I back in 1981\nBusiness math in 1983","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Alegrbra I bacj in ","Alegrbra I bac in ","Alegrbra I back in 1982","Alegrbra I back in 1981\nBusiness math in 1983"],"rt":66208,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":2022577,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":4977,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":2027573,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":5567,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":2033145,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":6760,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":2039908,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - not at all","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1 - not at all"],"rt":4398,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":2044308,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"3 - definitely","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3 - definitely"],"rt":3454,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":2047765,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Male","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Male"],"rt":3390,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":2051158,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is/are your native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"english","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["engilsh ","engilsh","engils","engil","engi","english"],"rt":12602,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":86,"time_elapsed":2063763,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["no"],"rt":4198,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":87,"time_elapsed":2067963,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"thanks!  Once this hit is accepted I am going to contact you so I can find out where to learn about math online.  It looks like I'm very rusty","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["thanks!  Once this hit is accepted I am going to contact w","thanks!  Once this hit is accepted I am going to contact you so I can find out where to learn about math online.  It looks lke I'm very rusty","thanks!  Once this hit is accepted I am going to contact you so I can find out where to learn about math online.  It looks like I'm very rusty"],"rt":53375,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":88,"time_elapsed":2121341,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"}]